<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
	<id>xfdashboard.desktop</id>
	<metadata_license>CC-BY-3.0</metadata_license>
	<project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
	<name>xfdashboard</name>
	<summary>Maybe a Gnome shell like dashboard for Xfce</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ca">Potser un tauler de control similar a Gnome Shell per a Xfce</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="da">Måske et instrumentbræt til Xfce i stil med det der findes i GNOME Shell</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="de">Ein Gnome Shell ähnliches Dashboard für Xfce</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="el">Ενδεχομένως ένα ταμπλό δραστηριοτήτων όμοιο με αυτό του κελύφους Gnome</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="es">Tal vez un intérprete de órdenes a modo de panel para Xfce</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="fr">Peut-être un shell GNOME comme un tableau de bord pour Xfce</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="gl">Un panel de control parecido ao intérprete de ordes Gnome para Xfce</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="he">אולי לוח מחוונים דומה Gnome עבור Xfce</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ie">Un panel de control por Xfce in li stil de Gnome shell</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="lt">Galbūt, į Gnome apvalkalą panašus skydelis, skirtas Xfce</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ru">Интерфейс GNOME shell, для среды Xfce</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sr">Полетник Иксфце-а који подсећа на Гномову шкољку</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="tr">Xfce için belki Gnome shell'e benzeyen bir kumanda paneli</summary>

	<description>
		<p>Xfdashboard provides a GNOME shell dashboard like interface for use with Xfce desktop.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ca">Xfdashboard proporciona una interfície de tauler de control similar a Gnome Shell per utilitzar amb l'escriptori Xfce.</p>
		<p xml:lang="da">Xfdashboard giver en grænseflade med et instrumentbræt til Xfce-skrivebordet i stil med det der findes i GNOME Shell.</p>
		<p xml:lang="de">Xfdashboard bietet ein GNOME Shell ähnliches Dashboard Interface für die Benützung mit dem Xfce Desktop an.</p>
		<p xml:lang="el">To Xfdashboard παρέχει μια διεπαφή όμοια με την επισκόπηση δραστηριοτήτων του κελύφους GNOME προς χρήση με το περιβάλλον εργασίας Xfce.</p>
		<p xml:lang="es">Xfdashboard provee un Intérprete de panel como el de GNOME para usarse en el entorno de escritorio Xfce.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fr">Xfdashboard fournit un tableau de bord shell GNOME comme interface pour une utilisation avec le bureau Xfce.</p>
		<p xml:lang="gl">O Xfdashboard fornece un interprete de ordes de panel de control Gnome para usar no escritorio Xfce</p>
		<p xml:lang="lt">Xfdashboard pateikia į Gnome apvalkalo skydelį panašią sąsają, skirtą naudoti Xfce darbalaukyje.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pl">Xfdashboard dostarcza interfejs wzorowany na panelu powłoki GNOME do użycia w Xfce.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ru">Xfdashboard предоставляет панель инструментов оболочки GNOME, как интерфейс для XFCE</p>
		<p xml:lang="sr">Полетник Иксфце-а је сучеље попут Гномове шкољке за употребу на радној површи Иксфце-а.</p>
		<p xml:lang="tr">Xfdashboard, Xfce masaüstüyle birlikte kullanılmak üzere bir GNOME kabuğu gösterge tablası gibi bir arabirim sağlar.</p>
		<p>It can be configured to run to any keyboard shortcut and when executed provides an overview of applications currently open enabling the user to switch between different applications. The search feature works like Xfce's app finder which makes it convenient to search for and start applications.</p>
		<p xml:lang="da">Det kan konfigureres til at køre med en hvilken som helst tastaturgenvej og når den udføres vises en oversigt med programmer som er åbne så brugeren kan skifte mellem dem. Søgefunktionaliteten virker ligesom i Xfce's programfinder hvilket gør det nemt at søge efter og starte programmer.</p>
		<p xml:lang="el">Μπορεί να ρυθμιστεί ώστε να εκτελείται με οποιαδήποτε εντολή και όταν εκτελείται παρέχει μια επισκόπηση των ανοιχτών εφαρμογών δίνοντας στο χρήστη τη δυνατότητα εναλλαγής μεταξύ διαφορετικών εφαρμογών. Η λειτουργία αναζήτησης λειτουργεί όπως η εύρεση εφαρμογών του Xfce πράγμα που καθιστά βολική την αναζήτηση και εκκίνηση εφαρμογών.</p>
		<p xml:lang="es">Puede ser configurado para funcionar con cualquier combinación de teclas y cuando se ejecuta proporciona una visión general de las aplicaciones que estén abiertas permitendo al usuario cambiar entre diferentes aplicaciones. La función de búsqueda funciona como el buscador de aplicaciones de Xfce que hace que sea conveniente para buscar e iniciar aplicaciones.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fr">Il peut être configuré pour fonctionner avec n'importe quel raccourci clavier et lorsqu'il est exécuté donne un aperçu des applications actuellement ouvertes permettant à l'utilisateur de basculer entre différentes applications. La fonction de recherche fonctionne comme l'application Finder de Xfce qui le rend pratique pour rechercher et démarrer des applications.</p>
		<p xml:lang="gl">Pode configurarse para se executar con calquera atallo de teclado e cando se executa fornece unha visión xeral dos aplicativos que están abertos permitindo ao usuario cambiar entre diferentes aplicativos. A función de busca funciona como buscador de aplicativos do Xfce o que fai que sexa útil para buscar e iniciar aplicativos.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pl">Może zostać skonfigurowany do uruchomienia pod dowolnym skrótem klawiszowym. Kiedy uruchomiony, wyświetla podgląd uruchomionych aplikacji i pozwala na przełączanie pomiędzy nimi. Funkcja wyszukiwania działa podobnie do Wyszukiwarki aplikacji Xfce, pozwalając szybciej uruchomić aplikacje.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ru">Он может быть сконфигурирован для работы с любым сочетанием клавиш и при выполнении обеспечивает обзор приложений открытых в настоящее время, позволяет пользователю переключаться между различными приложениями. Функция поиска работает как xfce App finder, что делает его удобным для поиска и запуска приложений.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sr">Може се подесити да се покреће на било коју пречицу дугмади, и када се изврши даје преглед тренутно отворених програма, омогућујући кориснику да прелази са једног програма на други. Претрага ради попут претраживача програма за Иксфце што чини полетника згодним за претрагу и покретање програма.</p>
		<p xml:lang="tr">Herhangi bir klavye kısayoluna gidecek şekilde yapılandırılabilir ve yürütülürken, kullanıcıların farklı uygulamalar arasında geçiş yapabilmeleri için halen açık olan uygulamalara genel bir bakış sağlar. Arama özelliği, uygulamaları aramak ve başlatmak için uygun Xfce'nin uygulama bulucusu gibi çalışır.</p>
	</description>

	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<image>http://docs.xfce.org/_media/apps/xfdashboard/starting-up.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>Browsing applications</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="ca">Navegació per les aplicacions</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="da">Gennemser programmer</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="de">Anwendungen durchsuchen</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="el">Περιήγηση στις εφαρμογές</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="es">Navegar por las aplicaciones</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="fr">Applications de navigation</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="gl">Navegación por aplicativos</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="he">סיור באפליקציות</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="ie">Navigation inter applicationes</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="pl">Przeglądanie aplikacji</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр приложений</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="sr">Преглед програма</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="tr">Uygulamar taranıyor</caption>
			<image>http://docs.xfce.org/_media/apps/xfdashboard/applications-view.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<caption>Searching applications</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="ca">Cerca d'aplicacions</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="da">Søger efter programmer</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="de">Suche Anwendungen</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="el">Αναζήτηση εφαρμογών</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="es">Buscar aplicaciones</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="fr">Applications de recherche</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="gl">Busca de aplicativos</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="he">חיפוש אפליקציות</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="ie">Sercha por applicationes</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="ja">アプリケーションを検索</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="pl">Wyszukiwanie aplikacji</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="ru">Поиск приложений</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="sr">Претрага програма</caption>
			<caption xml:lang="tr">Uygulamalar aranıyor</caption>
			<image>http://docs.xfce.org/_media/apps/xfdashboard/search-view.png</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>

	<url type="homepage">http://docs.xfce.org/apps/xfdashboard/start/</url>
	<url type="bugtracker">https://bugzilla.xfce.org</url>
	<url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/gmc-holle/xfdashboard/issues</url>
	<url type="help">http://docs.xfce.org/apps/xfdashboard/manual</url>

	<project_group>XFCE</project_group>

	<updatecontact>nomad@froevel.de</updatecontact>

	<provides>
		<binary>xfdashboard</binary>
	</provides>

	<kudos>
		<kudo>HiDpiIcon</kudo>
		<kudo>ModernToolkit</kudo>
	</kudos>

	<keywords>
		<keyword>window management</keyword>
		<keyword>application management</keyword>
		<keyword>organize</keyword>
		<keyword>search tool</keyword>
		<keyword>search</keyword>
	</keywords>

	<releases>
		<release version="0.7.7" timestamp="1600772127">
			<description>
				<p>This unstable development adds more animations as well as some smaller fixes.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="0.7.6" timestamp="1575026916">
			<description>
				<p>This unstable development adds animations.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="0.7.5" timestamp="1533679200">
			<description>
				<p>This unstable development adds support for touchpads and application actions (Jumplists, Quicklists) as well as new and updated translations.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="0.7.4" timestamp="1505796460">
			<description>
				<p>This unstable development adds lots of new and updated translations and support for newer xfconf versions.</p>
				<p xml:lang="fr">Ce développement instable ajoute de nombreuses traductions nouvelles et des mises à jour et prend en charge les nouvelles versions de xfconf.</p>
				<p xml:lang="gl">Esta versión inestábel de desenvolvemento engade moitas traducións novas e actualizadas e compatibilidade para novas versións de xfconf.</p>
				<p xml:lang="ru">Проект добавляет много новых и обновленных переводов и поддержку для новых версий xfconf.</p>
				<p xml:lang="tr">Bu kararsız gelişme, yeni xfconf sürümleri için birçok yeni ve güncellenmiş çeviri ve destek ekler.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="0.7.3" timestamp="1499409263">
			<description>
				<p>This unstable development implements a new experimental backend for GDK as well as it supports user stylesheets now.</p>
				<p xml:lang="fr">Ce développement instable implémente un nouvel arrière-plan expérimental pour GDK et prend désormais en charge les feuilles de style utilisateur.</p>
				<p xml:lang="gl">Esta versión inestábel de desenvolvemento engade de xeito experimental unha nova infraestrutura para GDK así como a compatibilidade para follas de estilo de usuario.</p>
				<p xml:lang="ru">Проект реализует новый экспериментальный бэкэнд для GDK, а также поддерживает пользовательские таблицы стилей.</p>
				<p xml:lang="tr">Bu kararsız gelişme, GDK için yeni bir deneysel arka plan uygular ve kullanıcı tarzlarını artık desteklemektedir.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="0.7.2" timestamp="1494826045">
			<description>
				<p>This unstable development improves loading performance of images and icon, adds a fine-grained debugging system and introduces an interface for multiple backends but only X11 is still the one only one supported.</p>
				<p xml:lang="fr">Ce développement instable améliore les performances de chargement des images et des icônes, ajoute un système de débogage à granularité fine et introduit une interface pour plusieurs moteurs de traitement, mais seul X11 est toujours celui qui est pris en charge.</p>
				<p xml:lang="gl">Esta versión inestábel de desenvolvemento mellora o desempeño de carga de imaxes e iconas. Engade un sistema de depuración de polo miudo e introduce unha interface para varias infraestruturas pero só o X11 segue sendo o único soportado.</p>
				<p xml:lang="ru">Проект повышает производительность загрузки изображений и значков, добавляет систему детальной отладки и вводит интерфейс для нескольких бэкэндов, но поддерживается только один X11.</p>
				<p xml:lang="tr">Bu kararsız gelişme, görüntülerin ve simgenin yüklenme performansını geliştirir, ince taneli bir hata ayıklama sistemi ekler ve çoklu arka planlar için bir arabirim sunar, ancak yalnızca X11 destekli olan yalnızca bir tanesidir.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="0.7.1" timestamp="1488792398">
			<description>
				<p>This unstable development introduces child windows shown next to the main window.</p>
				<p xml:lang="fr">Ce développement instable introduit les fenêtres enfants affichées à côté de la fenêtre principale.</p>
				<p xml:lang="gl">Esta versión inestábel de desenvolvemento insire sub xanelas amosadas á beira da xanela principal.</p>
				<p xml:lang="ru">Проект представляет дочерние окна, показанные рядом с главным окном.</p>
				<p xml:lang="tr">Bu kararsız gelişme, ana pencerenin yanında gösterilen çocuk pencerelerini tanıtır.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="0.6.1" timestamp="1482422594">
			<description>
				<p>This stable version fixes a bug setting the correct default applications at first use.</p>
				<p xml:lang="fr">Cette version stable corrige un bogue définissant les applications par défaut correctes lors de la première utilisation.</p>
				<p xml:lang="gl">Esta versión inestábel amaña un erro na configuración dos aplicativos predeterminados no primeiro uso.</p>
				<p xml:lang="ru">Эта версия исправляет ошибку определения правильных приложений по умолчанию при первом использовании.</p>
				<p xml:lang="tr">Bu kararlı sürüm, ilk kullanımda doğru varsayılan uygulamaları ayarlayan bir hatayı düzeltir.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="0.7.0" timestamp="1473183039">
			<description>
				<p>This unstable development introduces pop-up menus.</p>
				<p xml:lang="fr">Ce développement instable introduit des menus contextuels.</p>
				<p xml:lang="gl">Esta versión inestábel de desenvolvemento engade menús emerxentes.</p>
				<p xml:lang="ru">Проект представляет всплывающие меню.</p>
				<p xml:lang="tr">Bu kararsız gelişme, açılır menüler sunuyor.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
		<release version="0.6.0" timestamp="1463772864">
			<description>
				<p>This stable version introduces lots of new features like plugins and application tracker. It also contains a huge collection of other larger and smaller improvements.</p>
				<p xml:lang="fr">Cette version stable introduit de nombreuses nouvelles fonctionnalités telles que les greffons et le suivi des applications. Il contient également une énorme collection d'autres améliorations plus ou moins grandes.</p>
				<p xml:lang="gl">Esta versión estábel insire moitas funcións novas, como engadidos e seguimento de aplicativos. Tamén contén unha inxente cantidade de grandes e pequenas melloras.</p>
				<p xml:lang="ru">Эта версия представляет множество новых функций, таких как плагины и трекер приложений. Он также содержит огромную коллекцию других больших и маленьких улучшений.</p>
				<p xml:lang="tr">Bu kararlı sürüm, eklentiler ve uygulama izleyici gibi birçok yeni özellik sunar. Aynı zamanda diğer büyük ve küçük geliştirmelerden oluşan devasa bir koleksiyon da içerir.</p>
			</description>
		</release>
	</releases>
</component>